http://www.redlandscc.edu/privacy

ACADEMICS
Few colleges the size of Redlands have such a wide range of academic programs — not to mention the levels of excellence. Redlands houses a chapter of Phi Theta Kappa, the largest Honors Society for two-year colleges.
Undergraduates at Redlands get to be involved in conducting research. Plus, all classes are taught by the full professor: there are no graduate-student teachers.
Academics Home
Academic CalendarAcademic CatalogPrograms Of StudyHonors and Service Learning ProgramsTranscript Request2020 Graduation
Admissions
ADMISSIONS
We want you to have a positive and productive college experience right from the start! You can use our convenient online scheduler to arrange a campus tour.
Redlands welcomes many students who are the first in their family to pursue college, as well as students from around the world. Our staff is ready to help you throughout the process, sorting out any confusion about the process and any specific needs a student has.
Admissions Home
How to EnrollEnrollment Authorization FormCampus ToursConcurrent EnrollmentEventsInternational AdmissionsTestingViewbook
Athletics
ATHLETICS
Student athletes are another special attribute of the Redlands experience that gives all of us a little something more to cheer about. Both women's and men's teams have enjoyed their share of success, and our programs continue to grow.
Athletics
Men's BaseballMen's BasketballWomen's BasketballCross CountryWomen's GolfWomen's Soccer
About
ABOUT
Redlands is a unique place. Maybe that's why students feel so comfortable being themselves as students here: comfortable and confident pursuing their unique interests.
Redlands students feel like they are on familiar footing — with the opportunity to go anywhere! With programs from nursing to agricultural studies to the arts and sciences, Redlands students have gone on to excel across Oklahoma and beyond.
About Us
LeadershipCampus Map & DirectionsFacilities & ServicesInstitutional ComplianceJob BankPartnerships/GrantsRedlands FoundationTask Force on the Future of Higher EducationVendor Bid Opportunities
Life at Redlands
Life at Redlands
College is a big step: take it any direction you want to go at Redlands! From offering high quality on-campus housing in our modern apartments to providing game-day excitement with our men's and women's teams, this is no ordinary two-year school.
Our campus and our classes are sized right: you won't just be a face in the crowd at Redlands. Come and have the full college experience!
Life at Redlands
HandbooksBookstoreCampus Safety & SecurityCougar CornerFitness & WellnessStudent Housing at Cougar CrossingLearning Resources CenterStudent Clubs & OrganizationsStudent SupportTitle IX
Paying for Redlands
Paying for Redlands
A college education at Redlands costs less than the Oklahoma state average for public institutions (based on cost per credit hour). For students planning to attain a four-year degree, completing the first two at Redlands can save you thousands.
Figuring out the process of paying for college can be intimidating, especially in households where parents haven't gone themselves. We make it easy.
Paying for Redlands
Financial AssistanceConcurrentGPA CalculatorPayment & Refund OptionsScholarshipsTuition and FeesTop Financial Aid Questions
Menu
hii i
i
AcademicsAcademic CalendarAcademic CatalogPrograms Of StudyHonors and Service Learning ProgramsTranscript Request2020 Graduation
AdmissionsHow to EnrollEnrollment Authorization FormCampus ToursConcurrent EnrollmentEventsInternational AdmissionsTestingViewbook
AthleticsMen's BaseballMen's BasketballWomen's BasketballCross CountryWomen's GolfWomen's Soccer
AboutLeadershipCampus Map & DirectionsFacilities & ServicesInstitutional ComplianceJob BankPartnerships/GrantsRedlands FoundationTask Force on the Future of Higher EducationVendor Bid Opportunities
Life at RedlandsHandbooksBookstoreCampus Safety & SecurityCougar CornerFitness & WellnessStudent Housing at Cougar CrossingLearning Resources CenterStudent Clubs & OrganizationsStudent SupportTitle IX
Paying for RedlandsFinancial AssistanceConcurrentGPA CalculatorPayment & Refund OptionsScholarshipsTuition and FeesTop Financial Aid Questions
Current Students
X
Search
Search
Privacy Policy
Effective date: September 19, 2018
Redlands Community College ("us", "we", or "our") operates the https://www.redlandscc.edu website (the "Service").
This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of personal data when you use our Service and the choices you have associated with that data.
We use your data to provide and improve the Service. By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, accessible from https://www.redlandscc.edu
Information Collection And Use
We collect several different types of information for various purposes to provide and improve our Service to you.
Types of Data Collected
Personal Data
While using our Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you ("Personal Data"). Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to:
Email address
First name and last name
Phone number
Address, State, Province, ZIP/Postal code, City
Cookies and Usage Data
Usage Data
We may also collect information how the Service is accessed and used ("Usage Data"). This Usage Data may include information such as your computer's Internet Protocol address (e.g. IP address), browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data.
Tracking & Cookies Data
We use cookies and similar tracking technologies to track the activity on our Service and hold certain information.
Cookies are files with small amount of data which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored on your device. Tracking technologies also used are beacons, tags, and scripts to collect and track information and to improve and analyze our Service.
You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Service.
Examples of Cookies we use:
Session Cookies. We use Session Cookies to operate our Service.
Preference Cookies. We use Preference Cookies to remember your preferences and various settings.
Security Cookies. We use Security Cookies for security purposes.
Use of Data
Redlands Community College uses the collected data for various purposes:
To provide and maintain the Service
To notify you about changes to our Service
To allow you to participate in interactive features of our Service when you choose to do so
To provide customer care and support
To provide analysis or valuable information so that we can improve the Service
To monitor the usage of the Service
To detect, prevent and address technical issues
Transfer Of Data
Your information, including Personal Data, may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than those from your jurisdiction.
If you are located outside United States and choose to provide information to us, please note that we transfer the data, including Personal Data, to United States and process it there.
Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.
Redlands Community College will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy and no transfer of your Personal Data will take place to an organization or a country unless there are adequate controls in place including the security of your data and other personal information.
Disclosure Of Data
Legal Requirements
Redlands Community College may disclose your Personal Data in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:
To comply with a legal obligation
To protect and defend the rights or property of Redlands Community College
To prevent or investigate possible wrongdoing in connection with the Service
To protect the personal safety of users of the Service or the public
To protect against legal liability
Security Of Data
The security of your data is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Data, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.
Service Providers
We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service ("Service Providers"), to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related services or to assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.
These third parties have access to your Personal Data only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.
Analytics
We may use third-party Service Providers to monitor and analyze the use of our Service.
Google Analytics
Google Analytics is a web analytics service offered by Google that tracks and reports website traffic. Google uses the data collected to track and monitor the use of our Service. This data is shared with other Google services. Google may use the collected data to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.
You can opt-out of having made your activity on the Service available to Google Analytics by installing the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on. The add-on prevents the Google Analytics JavaScript (ga.js, analytics.js, and dc.js) from sharing information with Google Analytics about visits activity.
For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy & Terms web page: https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en
Links To Other Sites
Our Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party's site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.
We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.
Children's Privacy
Our Service does not address anyone under the age of 18 ("Children").
We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 18. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your Children has provided us with Personal Data, please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected Personal Data from children without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information from our servers.
Changes To This Privacy Policy
We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.
We will let you know via email and/or a prominent notice on our Service, prior to the change becoming effective and update the "effective date" at the top of this Privacy Policy.
You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.
Contact Us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us:
Safety, Behavioral Sciences, Business, Social Sciences and Performing Arts
© 2008-2020 Redlands Community College. Site by MRW.
Sitemap
Privacy
Accessibility Statement
